sitedoctors.net 2016-04-05

# Privacy Policy – SiteDoctors.net

## Privacy Policy Statement for SiteDoctors.net

###### SiteDoctors.net has created this privacy policy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: SiteDoctors.net

## OnlineHelper.info

###### OnlineHelper.info is our customer service and information site. OnlineHelper.org is simply a mirror of OnlineHelper.info. So if one site is unavailable, you can generally access the same information on the other site as they are hosted on 2 separate domains and networks.

###### These sites were added to give a central location for information concerning account setup and operation. The sites feature many demos and tutorials. Credit card customers may also see OnlineHelper.info on your billing statements and/or credit card statements for services purchased from SiteDoctors.net or our sister site MyCanadaOnline.com. All 3 sites mentioned above are wholly owned and operated by SiteDoctors.net and as such, our privacy policy and terms of use will apply unless otherwise specified by the site.

###### Information Automatically Logged

###### We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and your shopping cart.

## Cookies

Our Site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart, and to make sure you don’t see the same ad repeatedly. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, and to sometimes save your password so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our site.

## Advertisers

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad companies and we do not have access or control over this information. You should always note the website address (URL) of a cookie request. Cookies from us will specify SiteDoctors.net. If privacy is a concern, you should disallow cookies from all sites you do not know and trust.

## Order and Registration Forms

Our site’s registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name, email, and postal address), financial information (like their bank account or credit card numbers), unique identifiers and demographic information (such as zip code, phone number).

Contact information from the registration forms is used to ship purchases, information about our company. The customer’s contact information is also used to get in touch with the customer when necessary.

Financial information that is collected is used to check the users’ qualifications for registration, and to bill the user for products and services.

Unique identifiers are collected from Web site visitors to verify the user’s identity, and for use as account numbers in our record system.

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.  
We use this data to tailor our visitor’s experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

## Surveys

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like email address), and demographic information (like zip code, age, or income level).

Contact information from the surveys is used to ship purchases, information about our company. The customer’s contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary.

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.  
We use this data to tailor our visitor’s experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

## External Links

This site contains links to other sites. Although **SiteDoctors.net** attempts to screen all sites that we link to, **SiteDoctors.net** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

## Special Circumstances

There are some circumstances where information you provide needs to be shared with others. The following list is complete and contains all of the circumstances and other companies and/or agencies.

1 **Domain name registrations** and renewals require contact and ownership information to be submitted to the registrar. When a domain is registered, this information will be accessible by the general public via a WhoIs domain name search. The only information available to view will be information that you voluntarily submit. For your protection and at your request, **SiteDoctors.net** will use our own contact information in place of yours.

2 **Financial institutions** require your financial and personal identifier information in order to process credit card and/or check orders for products and/or services ordered. The information given will only be the information you release and will only be used for that purpose and only at the time/s that you authorize it for.

3 **Governmental and law enforcement agencies.** **SiteDoctors.net** does not and will not share your information with any company, government agency, news agency, individual, private or public institution unless requested by you or we are specifically instructed by a legally binding court order. And if such an order is delivered, all parties involved will be notified of the order, the information requested, and the agency listed as making the request.

## Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

## Supplementation of Information

This site supplements the information that you provide with information that is received from third parties such as financial institutions.

## Data Quality/Access

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided:

  1. You can log in to your personal account at http://billing.onlinehelper.info
  2. You can send email to support@onlinehelper.info

## Terms of Use

## SiteDoctors.net follows the strict guidelines of our customer privacy statement. Please make sure you understand this statement fully. Please click here to read the Terms of Use policy.

## Contacting Us

**For sales and general info:**

Email Address: **[Info@SiteDoctors.net](mailto:Info@SiteDoctors.net)**

Phone: **  1-844-SiteDoctors**

> ### **Have Support  
>  Questions?**
> 
> | We’ve created an extensive **customer support website**.  
>  Get info on every service we offer. The site features  
>  **detailed video demos and tutorials**.http://www.OnlineHelper.info or e-mail us at [Support@SiteDoctors.net](mailto:Support@SiteDoctors.net)  
> ---|---  
> | 
> 
> **SiteDoctors.net** still believes in customer service.
> 
> We offer 365 days a year 24/7 Internet chat,
> 
> email & toll free phone support. All hosting, DSL, Cable Internet and dial up accounts include
> 
> FREE EMAIL & EMAIL FORWARDING
> 
> Or try our **online chat!** Just click the chat icon to the left.
> 
> If we’re **online** , you’ll be able to **chat with us live** in real time.
> 
> Or leave us a message if we’re **offline**.
